<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<topic xmlns="http://www.imsglobal.org/xsd/imsccv1p1/imsdt_v1p1" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="http://www.imsglobal.org/xsd/imsccv1p1/imsdt_v1p1  http://www.imsglobal.org/profile/cc/ccv1p1/ccv1p1_imsdt_v1p1.xsd">
  <title>[T] Basic Discussion - Introduce Yourself</title>
  <text texttype="text/html">&lt;p&gt;An introduction discussion is useful way to initially engage with students and begin to establish some connection, particularly for remote courses (synch. or async.) Suggested text might include...&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;By now you've had the chance to get to know a bit about me from the course welcome video. I'd like to get to know all of you as well so that I can begin to learn more about how I can serve your goals and interests.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please take a few minutes to introduce yourself to the class. Some things you might want to share may include:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Where in the world are you? Since this is an online class, you might be in an exotic, far-flung location! Please share!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;What interests you about this class or degree?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;What's your professional background? Will this help your career?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;What do you like to do for fun?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;If you were in a room with your classmates, what board game would you ask them to play?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In other words, tell me something about you as a unique and special human being that lets us know the real you and  brings us all closer as a community!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 class="du-icon-instructions"&gt;Discussion Instructions&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;To introduce yourself, press "Reply" below.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You can write a response or...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;If you wish to post a video in the discussion, watch the brief tutorial below&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://dominicanu.instructure.com/courses/324330/pages/4-dot-3-submitting-a-panopto-recording-in-a-canvas-assignment-or-discussion?module_item_id=23985812" target="_blank" data-api-endpoint="https://dominicanu.instructure.com/api/v1/courses/324330/pages/4-dot-3-submitting-a-panopto-recording-in-a-canvas-assignment-or-discussion" data-api-returntype="Page"&gt;How to Submit a Video in a Canvas Assignment or Discussion&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</text>
</topic>
